Ying-Ying Szeto

yingyingszetoo@gmail.com

+1 (646) 421 3288

LinkedIn @yingyingszeto

PORTFOLIO

yingyingszeto.github.io/portfolio

EDUCATION

User Experience Design

Master • Falmouth University Falmouth, UK

Visual and Digital Art

Diploma • Humber College *Toronto, ON, Canada*

SKILLS

Design

UX Strategy

User Research

Interaction Design

Wireframing

Prototyping

Usability Testing

Visual Design

Tools

Figma

Miro

Mural

Optimal Workshop

HTML/CSS/JS

JIRA

LANGUAGE

English

Chinese

SUMMARY

UX / Product Designer with 5 years of experience. I specialize in end-toend product design and have delivered digital solutions for enterprises and startups (B2B and SaaS) in insurance, customer communication, and automotive marketplaces across North America and Asia. I am authorized to work in the US; no sponsorship required.

EXPERIENCE

Senior UX Designer

Mar 2021 - Aug 2023 • *Hong Kong*

Keyteo Consulting

Full-time Onsite at Manulife Financial (John Hancock)

B2B • Insurance

- Designed and delivered solutions that impacted 50k+ insurance agents across Hong Kong, Vietnam, the Philippines, Indonesia, and Malaysia.
- Led end-to-end design for multiple platforms across the sales workflow ecosystem, including mobile and web applications.
- Partnered with research and service design teams to conduct user studies and analysis, informing design decisions and influencing regional user experience strategies.

UX/UI Designer

Jan 2020 - Oct 2020 • *Hong Kong*

maaiiConnect

B2B SaaS • Customer Support

- Transformed the onboarding experience for SaaS product through a simple and delightful design to guide chatbot installation, reducing customer inquiry tickets by 30% in 2 months.
- Collaborated with product, engineering, and QA teams to ship pixelperfect production matching the design.

UX/UI Designer

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020 • *Hong Kong*

EAB Systems

B2B SaaS • Insurance

- Created user flows and interface design for client AXA Singapore, a global insurance company, based on a core SaaS product.
- Developed design concepts and pitched them to clients from various insurance enterprises.

Web Designer

Nov 2015 - Apr 2017 • *Toronto, ON, Canada*

autoTrader.ca

B2C • Automotive marketplace

 Collaborated with the UX team to improve the B2C automotive marketplace interface design.

Freelance Designer

2013 - Present

• Designed and developed websites for New Era Cap, Glo, Yuki Spa, and small businesses in Canada and Hong Kong.